sbsh.net 2013-09-20

# SafeWallet Privacy

## Privacy Policy - JUST ONLINE LTD

Effective date: November 14, 2012.

### Definitions

www.sbsh.net and www.safewallet.com (the "Web Site") is owned and operated by Just Online Ltd. 

The terms "Just", "we", "us", "our" and "ours" when used in this Privacy Policy mean Just Online Ltd. which includes all its parents, subsidiaries, divisions, branches, and affiliates.

The terms "you", "your" and "yours" when used in this Privacy Policy means any user of the Web Site and any one of the Apps.

The term "App" or "SafeWallet" when used in this Privacy Policy means the application known as SafeWallet Password Manager for mobile devices and personal computers, which is downloadable from the Web Site or other third party sources.

The term "Other Data" when used in this Privacy Policy refers to data and information provided by you as part of your registration and ongoing interaction with Just via the App and/or the Website and/or otherwise collected by Just. Other Data may include your name, date of birth, cell phone number, mailing address (physical and electronic), and other similar data and information (including personally identifiable information) provided by you, as well as information regarding your online activities such as purchases, websites visited and more.

The term "Secured Data" when used in this Privacy Policy refers to personally identifiable information about you or other private information that is entered by you into the App for safekeeping and not otherwise provided by you to Just in any manner (in written form, image, or otherwise), such as your ID numbers, usernames and passwords, credit card information and any other items of information entered by you into the App.

### General

This Privacy Policy describes Just's current policies and practices with regard to Other Data and Secured Data.

### Secured Data

Your security and privacy are our top priorities, therefore we built SafeWallet with the clear understanding that your Secured Data is private and that it should not be accessible to anyone, not even us. Secured Data entered by you is automatically encrypted locally on your device (and only then sent to our servers) and can only be decrypted by you, by entering your master password.

All of your Secured Data is stored on our servers only in its encrypted format, which it is not possible for us to decrypt. When you decide to transmit your Secured Data to third party sites, the transmission is done by way of a secure server. We use AES 256 BIT encryption along with additional security technologies to ensure the confidentiality of the Secured Data being transferred. 

### Acceptance

By accessing or browsing the Website, submitting information to, or other use of, any one of the Apps you consent to this Privacy Policy. You may not use the Web Site or the Apps or submit any information to Just if you do not agree to any of the terms herein.

### Collection of Other Data

We collect information from you when you register to be a Just user, place an order, subscribe to our newsletter (including via the Web Site), respond to a survey, fill out a form, or directly interact with us in any other way. Nevertheless, you may opt to visit our Web Site anonymously. 

### Use of Other Data

We process your Other Data to try to provide a safe, efficient, and customized experience, and only for specific and limited purposes. We ask only for data that is adequate, relevant and not excessive for those purposes.

### Some of these purposes include the following:

  * In order to inform you of new services we will be providing, or special offers, events or articles we think will be of interest to you; 
  * To personalize your experience (your information helps us better respond to your individual needs); 
  * To process transactions your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested; 
  * We may use your Other Data internally to help us improve our products and services including the Web Site and Apps and to improve customer service. 

### Disclosure of Other Data 

We do not share, sell or distribute your Other Data with unrelated third parties, except under these limited circumstances:

  * Other Data will be shared with certain third parties at your specific request, for example if you request to be sent further information regarding an ad you saw in the App. We cannot assure that these third parties will treat your information in accordance with this Privacy Policy.
  * Other Data may be shared with trusted third parties who assist us in operating our Web Site and Apps, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. However, non-personally identifiable information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.
  * We may share or transfer the information in our databases to comply with a legal requirement, for the administration of justice, to protect your vital interests, to protect the security or integrity of our databases or this Web Site, to take precautions against legal liability, or in the event of a corporate sale, merger, reorganization, dissolution or similar event.

Where appropriate, before disclosing Other Data to a third party, we contractually require the third party to take adequate precautions to protect that data.

### Anonymous Data Collected Through This Web Site

In addition to the information we collect as described above, we use technology to collect anonymous information about the use of our Web Site and the Apps. This collected information is completely anonymous and cannot in any way be linked to personal information; it simply enables us to compile statistics about our visitors and their usage habits, frequency, etc. The statistical information may be transmitted to third party sites.

We also use this anonymous data to improve the content and functionality of this Web Site, the Apps and our e-mail updates, to better understand our customers and markets, and to improve our products and services.

### Cookies

In order to collect the anonymous data described in the preceding paragraph, we may use "cookies" that collect the first level domain name of the user and the date and time you accessed this Web Site and any App. A cookie is a small file containing a string of characters. This information is sent to your computer when you use the Web Site and it's stored on your computer, subject to your cookies storage preferences, so that we can uniquely identify a user's browser.

We use cookies to help us remember and process the items in your shopping cart, understand and save your preferences for future visits, keep track of advertisements and compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer a better site experiences and tools in the future. We may contract with third-party service providers to assist us in better understanding our site visitors. These service providers are not permitted to use the information collected on our behalf except to help us conduct and improve our business.

We also use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server and to administer our Web Site. An IP address is a numeric code that identifies your computer on a network, or in this case, the Internet. Your IP address is also used to gather broad demographic information, such as determining the geographical regions of our visitors and users. 

### Third-Party Sites

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our Web Site, App or through our newsletter. It is your responsibility to read and understand their terms of use, privacy policy and any other instructions published by such sites prior to using their products or services. We will not be responsible for the policies or conduct of any third-party sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our Web Site and Apps and therefore welcome any feedback about these sites.

### Links to Other Web Sites

This Privacy Policy applies only to the Web Site and the Apps. This Web Site and App contains hyperlinks to web sites that are not operated by Just. These hyperlinks are provided for your reference and convenience only and do not imply any endorsement of the activities of these third-party web sites or any association with their operators. We do not control these web sites and are not responsible for their data collection or privacy practices. We urge you to review any privacy policy posted on any site you visit before using the site or providing any information about yourself.

### Transfer of Data Abroad

Just is a web-based global enterprise and has facilities and databases in different countries. We may, from time to time, transfer your Other Data and/or Secured Data (in encrypted form) to one of our databases in another country. If the level of privacy protection in a country does not comply with recognized international standards, we will ensure that data transferred to our databases in that country are adequately protected and that the transfer of data to third parties in such countries is made pursuant to a contract or other measures providing adequate protection.

Of course, the Internet is made up of a large number of international connections. If you are visiting this Web Site from a country other than the country in which our server is located, the various communications will necessarily result in the transfer of information across international boundaries. By visiting this Web Site and/or installing an App and communicating electronically with us, you consent to these transfers.

### Just Email Marketing Communication Policy

Just sends promotional email only to:

  * Customers;
  * People who have given consent to Just to receive promotional email;
  * People on rented email lists who have given permission to the list owner to receive third-party promotional email;
  * All of the abovementioned who have not opted out after having received promotional email from us.

In each promotional email, we include an easy and clear way to opt out of future Just emails. Opt out requests are submitted through our Web Site and such opt out requests are processed automatically and within one business day. When sending email to rented email lists, we suppress addresses of those people who have opted out of Just emails in the past. We always disclose our identity in mass email communications, including the address of our headquarters location.

We never use deceiving header information or subject lines.

We never send mass, promotional email to email addresses "harvested" from websites.

We never, under any circumstances, rent or sell email addresses to any other company or individual.

Our marketing email policy and practice fully conforms to the United States Federal "CAN SPAM" act of 2003 and the applicable Israeli statues such as the Protection of Privacy Law 5741-1981. Note that some regions such as the European Union, have different email laws and guidelines, and Just aims to conform to local laws in those cases. We welcome and encourage your thoughts on this policy at support[at]safewallet[dőt]com.

### User Communications

When you send email or other communications to Just, we may retain those communications in order to process your inquiries, respond to your requests and improve our services.

### Special Note for Parents and Children Under Age 13

The site you are visiting is a general audience site. The Web Site is not directed to persons under 13. If a parent or guardian becomes aware that his or her child has provided us with personal information without their consent, he or she should contact us. We do not knowingly collect or solicit personal information from people under 13. If we become aware that a person under 13 has provided us with personal information, we will delete such information from our files.

### Terms and Conditions

Please see our Terms and Conditions establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of the Web Site and the Apps, at: http://www.safewallet.com.

### Changes to This Policy

This Policy may change from time to time. We will post any Policy changes on this page and, if the changes are significant, we will provide a more prominent notice. You are encouraged to check for the latest Policy as often as you wish. Each version of this Policy will be identified at the top of the page by its effective date, and we will also keep prior versions of this Policy in an archive for your review. We will never change this Policy in such a way that would compromise the confidentiality of your Secured Data.

### Contacting Us

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy or concerns about the way we process your Other Data and/or Secured Data, please contact us by e-mailing us at support[at]safewallet[dőt]com.
